{
    "subject": "resource/James_Kay_(Kentucky_politician)",
    "predicate": "property/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Kentucky",
    "human_readable": "The alma mater of James Kay (Kentucky politician) is University of Kentucky.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.955027163028717,
            "question": "Is James Kay a politician from Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9513979554176331,
            "question": "Is James Kay a graduate of the University of Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8720439672470093,
            "question": "Did James Kay attend college in Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8670585751533508,
            "question": "Name James Kay's alma mater."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8567857146263123,
            "question": "What university is James Kay's alma mater?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8310831189155579,
            "question": "What is the name of the politician who graduated from the University of Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6867170929908752,
            "question": "What state is the University of Kentucky in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.636565089225769,
            "question": "What is the name of the university that James Kay attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5378069877624512,
            "question": "To which university did James Kay graduate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45632901787757874,
            "question": "Where did James Kay go to college?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The alma mater of James Kay (Kentucky politician) is University of Kentucky.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3559_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which university did James Kay graduate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3559_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the university that James Kay attended?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3559_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is the University of Kentucky in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3559_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3559_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3559_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3559_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3559_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3559_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3559_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3559_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3559_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3559_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3559_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to the document, James L. Kay II earned his BA in history and political science from the University of Kentucky."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents states that \"Kay earned his BA in history and political science from the University of Kentucky,\" which supports the query that the alma mater of James Kay (Kentucky politician) is University of Kentucky."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}